ucbi.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy | United Community Bank

FACTS | **WHAT DOES UNITED COMMUNITY BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
---|---  
Why? | 

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
  
What? | 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * **Social Security number and income**
  * **Account balances and payment history**
  * **Credit history and Employment information**

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.  
  
How? | 

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons United Community Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  
  
Reasons we can share your personal information | Does United Community Bank share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes—**  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court valid orders and as required by law, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes—**  
to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—**  
information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—**  
information about your creditworthiness | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
  
What we do  
---  
**How does United Community Bank protect my personal information?** | 

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
  
**How does United Community Bank collect my personal information?** | 

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * apply for a loan or give us your income information
  * open an account or make deposits or withdrawals from your account
  * use your credit or debit card

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.  
  
**Why can’t I limit all sharing?** | 

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  
  
Definitions  
---  
**Affiliates** | 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _Our affiliates include others, such as Our Mortgage Company and Advisory Services._

**Nonaffiliates** | 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * _United Community Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you_

**Joint  marketing** | 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * _Our joint marketing partners include Credit Card Companies_

#### Security Statement

United Community Bank is committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your personal information. Technology and new marketing practices have increased the amount of customer information collected and shared in today's marketplace. Consumers are concerned about the impact this development has or might have on their privacy and security. We are sensitive to these concerns and we are committed to taking reasonable steps to protect the privacy and security of information shared with us. Our customers are protected not only by state and federal laws, but more importantly, our commitment to them.

To help us offer secure online banking services, United Community Bank uses industry-standard technology and procedures. This technology allows us to properly authenticate your identity and protect your information when you access our online banking services.

We maintain rigorous security standards and procedures to prevent unauthorized access to customer information. We issue a unique Access ID and Password that identify the customer when logging on to our website Online Banking or Mobile Banking App. We use state of the art secured software for transferring data together with a very high level of encryption bit strength. Our security software also ensures that users establish sessions with only secure websites. The software further protects data by (1) authentication which ensures that the customer is actually communicating with the bank and not someone impersonating the bank; (2) encryption or scrambling of transferred data so that account information cannot be intercepted and read by a third party; and (3) assessing the data integrity by verifying that the information sent by the customer to the bank has not been altered during the transfer.

Our Security Center provides additional resources and information about best practices to safeguard your accounts and identity.
